export const DummyQuizData = [
	
    {
        topic_id : "2",
        data : [
			{
				key: 1,
				question: "Animal",
				answer: "dou butsu"
			},
			{
				key: 2,
				question: "Zebra",
				answer: "shimauma"
			},
			{
				key: 3,
				question: "Sheep",
				answer: "hitsuji"
			},
			{
				key: 4,
				question: "Goat",
				answer: "yagi"
			},
			{
				key: 5,
				question: "Deer",
				answer: "shika"
			},
			{
				key: 6,
				question: "Hippopotamus",
				answer: "kaba"
			},
			{
				key: 7,
				question: "Panda",
				answer: "Panda"
			},
			{
				key: 8,
				question: "Giraffe",
				answer: "kirin"
			},
			{
				key: 9,
				question: "Pig",
				answer: "buta"
			},
			{
				key: 10,
				question: "Wild Boar",
				answer: "inoshishi"
			},
			{
				key: 11,
				question: "Eagle",
				answer: "washi"
			},
			{
				key: 12,
				question: "Bat",
				answer: "koumori"
			},
			{
				key: 13,
				question: "Bird",
				answer: "tori"
			},
			{
				key: 14,
				question: "Crow",
				answer: "karasu"
			},
			{
				key: 15,
				question: "Wild Duck",
				answer: "kamo"
			},
			{
				key: 16,
				question: "Domestic Duck",
				answer: "ahiru"
			},
			{
				key: 17,
				question: "Chicken",
				answer: "niwatori"
			},
			{
				key: 18,
				question: "Dog",
				answer: "inu"
			},
			{
				key: 19,
				question: "Kitten",
				answer: "ko neko"
			},
			{
				key: 20,
				question: "Cat",
				answer: "neko"
			}
		]
    },
    {
        topic_id : "1",
        data : [
			{
				key: 1, 
				question: 'a little', 
				answer: 'ちょっと'
			},
			{key: 2, question: 'a little (more formal than ちょっと)', answer: 'すこし (少し)'}
			,
			{key: 3, question: 'a little more', answer: 'もうすこし (もう少し)'}
			,
			{key: 4, question: 'a little more', answer: 'もうちょっと'}
			,
			{key: 5, question: 'about ~', answer: '～について ([Noun] + について)'}
			,
			{key: 6, question: 'academic grade; academic result', answer: 'せいせき (成績)'}
			,
			{key: 7, question: 'according to ~', answer: '～によると ([Noun] + によると)'}
			,
			{key: 8, question: 'Africa', answer: 'アフリカ'}
			,
			{key: 9, question: 'after that; and (then)', answer: 'それから'}
			,
			{key: 10, question: 'afternoon', answer: 'ごご (午後)'}
			,
			{key: 11, question: '~ ago (e.g. 3年前 (さんねんまえ): three years ago; 15日前 (じゅうごにちまえ): fifteen days ago)', answer: '〜まえ ([Duration] + 前)'}
			,
			{key: 12, question: 'air conditioner', answer: 'クーラー'}
			,
			{key: 13, question: 'airplane', answer: 'ひこうき (飛行機)'}
			,
			{key: 14, question: 'airport', answer: 'くうこう (空港)'}
			,
			{key: 15, question: 'alcohol; sake', answer: 'おさけ (お酒)'}
			,
			{key: 16, question: 'all', answer: 'ぜんぶ (全部)'}
			,
			{key: 17, question: 'almost', answer: 'ほとんど'}
			,
			{key: 18, question: 'alone; by oneself (一人 (ひとり): one person)', answer: 'ひとりで (一人で)'}
			,
			{key: 19, question: 'already; not anymore', answer: 'もう'}
			,
			{key: 20, question: 'always', answer: 'いつも'}
			,
			{key: 21, question: ' (to be) amazing', answer: 'すごい (すごい)'}
			,
			{key: 22, question: 'America', answer: 'アメリカ'}
			,
			{key: 23, question: 'and then', answer: 'そして'}
			,
			{key: 24, question: 'anime (Japanese animation)', answer: 'アニメ'}
			,
			{key: 25, question: 'announcer; newscaster', answer: 'アナウンサー'}
			,
			{key: 26, question: 'to answer', answer: 'こたえる (答える)'}
			,
			{key: 27, question: 'anyone; whoever', answer: 'だれでも (誰でも)'}
			,
			{key: 28, question: 'apartment', answer: 'アパート'}
			,
			{key: 29, question: 'to apologize', answer: 'あやまる (謝る)'}
			,
			{key: 30, question: 'apple', answer: 'りんご'}
			,
			{key: 31, question: 'around [time]; about [time]', answer: '～ごろ'}
			,
			{key: 32, question: 'around/about/approximately ~', answer: '〜ぐらい'}
			,
			{key: 33, question: 'to arrive', answer: 'つく (着く)'}
			,
			{key: 34, question: 'art museum', answer: 'びじゅつかん (美術館)'}
			,
			{key: 35, question: 'Asakusa [name of a district in Tokyo]', answer: 'あさくさ (浅草)'}
			,
			{key: 36, question: 'Asia', answer: 'アジア'}
			,
			{key: 37, question: 'Australia', answer: 'オーストラリア'}
			,
			{key: 38, question: 'autumn; fall', answer: 'あき (秋)'}
			,
			{key: 39, question: 'baby', answer: 'あかちゃん (赤ちゃん)'}
			,
			{key: 40, question: 'back; behind', answer: 'うしろ (後ろ)'}
			,
			{key: 41, question: 'back; height', answer: 'せ (背)'}
			,
			{key: 42, question: ' (to be) bad', answer: 'わるい (悪い)'}
			,
			{key: 43, question: 'bag', answer: 'かばん'}
			,
			{key: 44, question: "baggage; one's belongings", answer: 'にもつ (荷物)'}
			,
			{key: 45, question: 'ball', answer: 'ボール'}
			,
			{key: 46, question: 'bank', answer: 'ぎんこう (銀行)'}
			,
			{key: 47, question: 'bath (お風呂に入る (おふろにはいる): to take a bath)', answer: 'おふろ (お風呂)'}
			,
			{key: 48, question: '"bathroom (American); toilet (British) (refers to the room', answer: ' not the fixture)"'}
			,
			{key: 49, question: 'to be (honorific expression of 〜だ)', answer: '〜でいらっしゃる ( (long form is ～でいらっしゃいます))'}
			,
			{key: 50, question: 'to be (politer expression of 〜だ)', answer: '〜でござる ( (long form is ～でございます))'}
			,
			{key: 51, question: 'to be crowded/congested', answer: 'こむ (込む)'}
			,
			{key: 52, question: 'to be late', answer: 'おくれる (遅れる)'}
			,
			{key: 53, question: 'to be; exist', answer: 'いる'}
			,
			{key: 54, question: 'to be; have; exist', answer: 'ある'}
			,
			{key: 55, question: '"be; is; am; are (when expressing equivalency such as in ""X is Y"" (X=Y).)"', answer: 'だ'}
			,
			{key: 56, question: 'to become (e.g. 先生になる (せんせいになる): to become a teacher)', answer: 'なる'}
			,
			{key: 57, question: 'beef', answer: 'ぎゅうにく (牛肉)'}
			,
			{key: 58, question: 'beer', answer: 'ビール'}
			,
			{key: 59, question: 'to begin; start (something)', answer: 'はじめる (始める)'}
			,
			{key: 60, question: ' (something) begins', answer: 'はじまる (始まる)'}
			,
			{key: 61, question: 'below; under', answer: 'した (下)'}
			,
			{key: 62, question: 'between', answer: 'あいだ (間)'}
			,
			{key: 63, question: 'bicycle', answer: 'じてんしゃ (自転車)'}
			,
			{key: 64, question: ' (to be) big', answer: 'おおきい (大きい)'}
			,
			{key: 65, question: 'bird', answer: 'とり (鳥)'}
			,
			{key: 66, question: 'birthday', answer: 'たんじょうび (誕生日)'}
			,
			{key: 67, question: ' (the color) black', answer: 'くろ (黒)'}
			,
			{key: 68, question: ' (to be) black', answer: 'くろい (黒い)'}
			,
			{key: 69, question: 'to bloom', answer: 'さく (咲く)'}
			,
			{key: 70, question: ' (the color) blue', answer: 'あお (青)'}
			,
			{key: 71, question: ' (to be) blue', answer: 'あおい (青い)'}
			,
			{key: 72, question: 'book', answer: 'ほん (本)'}
			,
			{key: 73, question: 'bookstore', answer: 'ほんや (本屋)'}
			,
			{key: 74, question: ' (to be) boring', answer: 'つまらない'}
			,
			{key: 75, question: 'to borrow', answer: 'かりる (借りる)'}
			,
			{key: 76, question: 'boss; work superior', answer: 'じょうし (上司)'}
			,
			{key: 77, question: 'Brazil', answer: 'ブラジル'}
			,
			{key: 78, question: 'bread', answer: 'パン'}
			,
			{key: 79, question: 'to break (something)', answer: 'こわす (壊す)'}
			,
			{key: 80, question: 'breakfast', answer: 'あさごはん (朝ご飯)'}
			,
			{key: 81, question: ' (something) breaks', answer: 'こわれる (壊れる)'}
			,
			{key: 82, question: 'to bring [something] (cf. 持って行く (もっていく): to take [something]) ', answer: 'もってくる (持って来る)'}
			,
			{key: 83, question: 'brother; sibling', answer: 'きょうだい (兄弟)'}
			,
			{key: 84, question: ' (the color) brown', answer: 'ちゃいろ (茶色)'}
			,
			{key: 85, question: ' (to be) brown', answer: 'ちゃいろい (茶色い)'}
			,
			{key: 86, question: 'to build', answer: 'たてる (建てる)'}
			,
			{key: 87, question: 'building', answer: 'たてもの (建物)'}
			,
			{key: 88, question: 'bus', answer: 'バス'}
			,
			{key: 89, question: ' (to be) busy', answer: 'いそがしい (忙しい)'}
			,
			{key: 90, question: 'but', answer: 'でも'}
			,
			{key: 91, question: 'button', answer: 'ボタン'}
			,
			{key: 92, question: 'to buy', answer: 'かう (買う)'}
			,
			{key: 93, question: 'cafeteria', answer: 'しょくどう (食堂)'}
			,
			{key: 94, question: 'cake', answer: 'ケーキ'}
			,
			{key: 95, question: 'calendar', answer: 'カレンダー'}
			,
			{key: 96, question: 'to call [on the phone]', answer: 'でんわする (電話する)'}
			,
			{key: 97, question: 'can do; be able to do (potential form of する)', answer: 'できる (出来る)'}
			,
			{key: 98, question: 'candy', answer: 'あめ (飴)'}
			,
			{key: 99, question: 'car', answer: 'くるま (車)'}
			,
			{key: 100, question: 'to carry', answer: 'はこぶ (運ぶ)'}
			,
			{key: 101, question: 'case', answer: 'ケース (ケース)'}
			,
			{key: 102, question: 'cat', answer: 'ねこ (猫)'}
			,
			{key: 103, question: 'CD', answer: 'CD (シーディー)'}
			,
			{key: 104, question: 'cell phone', answer: 'けいたいでんわ (携帯電話)'}
			,
			{key: 105, question: 'chair', answer: 'いす (椅子)'}
			,
			{key: 106, question: 'check', answer: 'チェック'}
			,
			{key: 107, question: 'to check', answer: 'チェックする'}
			,
			{key: 108, question: 'chicken', answer: 'とりにく (とり肉)'}
			,
			{key: 109, question: 'child', answer: 'こども (子供)'}
			,
			{key: 110, question: 'child  (honorific expression of 子供（こども）)', answer: 'おこさん (お子さん)'}
			,
			{key: 111, question: 'China', answer: 'ちゅうごく (中国)'}
			,
			{key: 112, question: 'Christmas', answer: 'クリスマス'}
			,
			{key: 113, question: 'cigarette', answer: 'たばこ'}
			,
			{key: 114, question: 'circle; yen', answer: 'えん (円)'}
			,
			{key: 115, question: 'class', answer: 'クラス'}
			,
			{key: 116, question: 'class', answer: 'じゅぎょう (授業)'}
			,
			{key: 117, question: 'classmate', answer: 'クラスメート'}
			,
			{key: 118, question: 'classroom', answer: 'きょうしつ (教室)'}
			,
			{key: 119, question: 'to clean', answer: 'そうじする (掃除する)'}
			,
			{key: 120, question: 'clean; beautiful', answer: 'きれい（な）'}
			,
			{key: 121, question: 'cleaning', answer: 'そうじ (掃除)'}
			,
			{key: 122, question: 'to climb', answer: 'のぼる (登る)'}
			,
			{key: 123, question: 'clock; watch', answer: 'とけい (時計)'}
			,
			{key: 124, question: 'to close (something)', answer: 'しめる (閉める)'}
			,
			{key: 125, question: ' (something) closes', answer: 'しまる (閉まる)'}
			,
			{key: 126, question: 'clothes', answer: 'ふく (服)'}
			,
			{key: 127, question: 'cloudy', answer: 'くもり (曇り)'}
			,
			{key: 128, question: 'coffee', answer: 'コーヒー'}
			,
			{key: 129, question: 'coffee shop; café', answer: 'きっさてん (喫茶店)'}
			,
			{key: 130, question: ' (to be) cold (refers to atmospheric temperature and not the temperature of objects)', answer: 'さむい (寒い)'}
			,
			{key: 131, question: ' (to be) cold (refers to the temperature of objects and not to atmospheric temperature)', answer: 'つめたい (冷たい)'}
			,
			{key: 132, question: 'color', answer: 'いろ (色)'}
			,
			{key: 133, question: 'to come', answer: 'くる (来る)'}
			,
			{key: 134, question: 'to come out', answer: 'でてくる (出てくる)'}
			,
			{key: 135, question: 'company', answer: 'かいしゃ (会社)'}
			,
			{key: 136, question: 'company president', answer: 'しゃちょう (社長)'}
			,
			{key: 137, question: 'computer', answer: 'コンピューター'}
			,
			{key: 138, question: 'conference room', answer: 'かいぎしつ (会議室)'}
			,
			{key: 139, question: 'to consult; confer with', answer: 'そうだんする (相談する)'}
			,
			{key: 140, question: 'to continue', answer: 'つづける (続ける)'}
			,
			{key: 141, question: 'convenience store', answer: 'コンビニ (コンビニ)'}
			,
			{key: 142, question: 'convenient; useful', answer: 'べんり（な） (便利（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 143, question: 'conversation', answer: 'かいわ (会話)'}
			,
			{key: 144, question: 'cooking; cuisine', answer: 'りょうり (料理)'}
			,
			{key: 145, question: ' (to be) cool (-looking); good-looking', answer: 'かっこいい'}
			,
			{key: 146, question: 'copy', answer: 'コピー'}
			,
			{key: 147, question: '[counter for people]', answer: '～にん (〜人)'}
			,
			{key: 148, question: 'country', answer: 'くに (国)'}
			,
			{key: 149, question: 'to cry', answer: 'なく (泣く)'}
			,
			{key: 150, question: 'to cut', answer: 'きる (切る)'}
			,
			{key: 151, question: ' (to be) cute', answer: 'かわいい'}
			,
			{key: 152, question: 'to dance', answer: 'おどる (踊る)'}
			,
			{key: 153, question: ' (to be) dangerous', answer: 'あぶない (危ない)'}
			,
			{key: 154, question: ' (to be) dark', answer: 'くらい (暗い)'}
			,
			{key: 155, question: 'day after tomorrow', answer: 'あさって'}
			,
			{key: 156, question: 'daytime', answer: 'ひる (昼)'}
			,
			{key: 157, question: ' (to be) delicious; good[-tasting]; ', answer: 'おいしい'}
			,
			{key: 158, question: 'dentist', answer: 'はいしゃ (歯医者)'}
			,
			{key: 159, question: 'department head [at a company]', answer: 'ぶちょう (部長)'}
			,
			{key: 160, question: 'department store', answer: 'デパート'}
			,
			{key: 161, question: 'desk; table', answer: 'つくえ (机)'}
			,
			{key: 162, question: 'diary; journal', answer: 'にっき (日記)'}
			,
			{key: 163, question: 'dictionary', answer: 'じしょ (辞書)'}
			,
			{key: 164, question: 'to die; pass away', answer: 'しぬ (死ぬ)'}
			,
			{key: 165, question: ' (to be) different; to differ', answer: 'ちがう (違う)'}
			,
			{key: 166, question: ' (to be) difficult', answer: 'むずかしい (難しい)'}
			,
			{key: 167, question: 'digital camera', answer: 'デジタルカメラ'}
			,
			{key: 168, question: 'dinner', answer: 'ばんごはん (晩ご飯)'}
			,
			{key: 169, question: ' (to be) dirty', answer: 'きたない (汚い)'}
			,
			{key: 170, question: 'to disappear; run out', answer: 'なくなる'}
			,
			{key: 171, question: 'disappointing', answer: 'ざんねん（な） (残念（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 172, question: 'disliked; to dislike', answer: 'きらい（な） (嫌い（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 173, question: 'to do', answer: 'する'}
			,
			{key: 174, question: 'to do (courteous expression of する)', answer: 'いたす'}
			,
			{key: 175, question: 'to do (honorific expression of する)', answer: 'なさる ( (long form is なさいます))'}
			,
			{key: 176, question: 'to do; to give (more casual than する and あげる)', answer: 'やる'}
			,
			{key: 177, question: 'doctor', answer: 'いしゃ (医者)'}
			,
			{key: 178, question: 'dog', answer: 'いぬ (犬)'}
			,
			{key: 179, question: 'door', answer: 'ドア'}
			,
			{key: 180, question: 'dormitory', answer: 'りょう (寮)'}
			,
			{key: 181, question: 'drama', answer: 'ドラマ'}
			,
			{key: 182, question: 'dream', answer: 'ゆめ (夢)'}
			,
			{key: 183, question: 'dress', answer: 'ドレス'}
			,
			{key: 184, question: 'to drink', answer: 'のむ (飲む)'}
			,
			{key: 185, question: 'drink; beverage', answer: 'のみもの (飲み物)'}
			,
			{key: 186, question: 'to drive', answer: 'うんてんする (運転する)'}
			,
			{key: 187, question: ' (to be) early', answer: 'はやい (早い)'}
			,
			{key: 188, question: 'to eat', answer: 'たべる (食べる)'}
			,
			{key: 189, question: 'to eat; to drink (honorific expression of 食べる（たべる）and 飲む（のむ）)', answer: 'めしあがる (召し上がる)'}
			,
			{key: 190, question: '"to eat; to drink to receive (humble expression of 食べる（たべる）', answer: ' 飲む（のむ）and もらう)"'}
			,
			{key: 191, question: 'economy', answer: 'けいざい (経済)'}
			,
			{key: 192, question: 'education', answer: 'きょういく (教育)'}
			,
			{key: 193, question: 'Egypt', answer: 'エジプト'}
			,
			{key: 194, question: 'eight', answer: 'はち (八)'}
			,
			{key: 195, question: 'electricity; electric light', answer: 'でんき (電気)'}
			,
			{key: 196, question: 'elementary school', answer: 'しょうがっこう (小学校)'}
			,
			{key: 197, question: 'elevator', answer: 'エレベーター'}
			,
			{key: 198, question: 'email; text message', answer: 'メール'}
			,
			{key: 199, question: 'emoji', answer: 'えもじ (絵文字)'}
			,
			{key: 200, question: ' (something) ends; finishes', answer: 'おわる (終わる)'}
			,
			{key: 201, question: 'English', answer: 'えいご (英語)'}
			,
			{key: 202, question: ' (to be) enjoyable; joyful; pleasant', answer: 'たのしい (楽しい)'}
			,
			{key: 203, question: 'to enter (e.g. レストランに入る (はいる): to enter a restaurant)', answer: 'はいる (入る)'}
			,
			{key: 204, question: 'entrance', answer: 'いりぐち (入り口)'}
			,
			{key: 205, question: 'essay; composition', answer: 'さくぶん (作文)'}
			,
			{key: 206, question: 'Europe', answer: 'ヨーロッパ'}
			,
			{key: 207, question: 'evening', answer: 'ばん (晩)'}
			,
			{key: 208, question: 'every day', answer: 'まいにち (毎日)'}
			,
			{key: 209, question: 'every month', answer: 'まいげつ ／まいつき (毎月)'}
			,
			{key: 210, question: 'every morning', answer: 'まいあさ (毎朝)'}
			,
			{key: 211, question: 'every night', answer: 'まいばん (毎晩)'}
			,
			{key: 212, question: 'every week', answer: 'まいしゅう (毎週)'}
			,
			{key: 213, question: 'every year', answer: 'まいとし ／まいねん (毎年)'}
			,
			{key: 214, question: 'everyone', answer: 'みんな'}
			,
			{key: 215, question: 'everyone (often as a formal way of addressing a group of listeners)', answer: 'みなさん (皆さん)'}
			,
			{key: 216, question: 'Excuse me.; Goodbye. (to a teacher)', answer: 'しつれいします (失礼します)'}
			,
			{key: 217, question: 'to exercise', answer: 'うんどうする (運動する)'}
			,
			{key: 218, question: 'to exist; be (courteous expression of いる)', answer: 'おる'}
			,
			{key: 219, question: 'to exist; to be (politer expression of ある)', answer: 'ござる ( (long form is ございます))'}
			,
			{key: 220, question: '"to exist; be; to go; to come (honorific expression of いる', answer: ' 行く（いく） and 来る（くる）)" (いらっしゃる)'}
			,
			{key: 221, question: 'experience', answer: 'けいけん (経験)'}
			,
			{key: 222, question: 'to explain', answer: 'せつめいする (説明する)'}
			,
			{key: 223, question: 'expression', answer: 'ひょうげん (表現)'}
			,
			{key: 224, question: 'eye', answer: 'め (目)'}
			,
			{key: 225, question: 'family', answer: 'かぞく (家族)'}
			,
			{key: 226, question: 'famous', answer: 'ゆうめい（な） (有名（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 227, question: 'famous person; celebrity', answer: 'ゆうめいじん (有名人)'}
			,
			{key: 228, question: ' (to be) fast', answer: 'はやい (速い)'}
			,
			{key: 229, question: 'fast', answer: 'はやく (速く)'}
			,
			{key: 230, question: 'father', answer: 'おとうさん (お父さん)'}
			,
			{key: 231, question: "[one's own] father", answer: 'ちち (父)'}
			,
			{key: 232, question: 'file', answer: 'ファイル'}
			,
			{key: 233, question: 'to find', answer: 'みつける (見つける)'}
			,
			{key: 234, question: 'fish', answer: 'さかな (魚)'}
			,
			{key: 235, question: 'fishing', answer: 'つり (釣り)'}
			,
			{key: 236, question: 'five', answer: 'ご (五)'}
			,
			{key: 237, question: 'to fix', answer: 'なおす (直す)'}
			,
			{key: 238, question: '~ floor', answer: '〜かい (～階)'}
			,
			{key: 239, question: 'flower', answer: 'はな (花)'}
			,
			{key: 240, question: 'folder', answer: 'フォルダー'}
			,
			{key: 241, question: 'folk', answer: 'フォーク'}
			,
			{key: 242, question: 'food', answer: 'たべもの (食べ物)'}
			,
			{key: 243, question: 'foot; leg', answer: 'あし (足)'}
			,
			{key: 244, question: 'for the first time', answer: 'はじめて (初めて)'}
			,
			{key: 245, question: 'foreign country', answer: 'がいこく (外国)'}
			,
			{key: 246, question: 'to forget', answer: 'わすれる (忘れる)'}
			,
			{key: 247, question: 'four', answer: 'よん／し (四)'}
			,
			{key: 248, question: 'France', answer: 'フランス'}
			,
			{key: 249, question: 'free/spare (time)', answer: 'ひま（な） (暇（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 250, question: 'Friday', answer: 'きんようび (金曜日)'}
			,
			{key: 251, question: 'friend', answer: 'ともだち (友達)'}
			,
			{key: 252, question: 'from now; starting now; after this', answer: 'これから'}
			,
			{key: 253, question: 'front; before', answer: 'まえ (前)'}
			,
			{key: 254, question: 'future', answer: 'しょうらい (将来)'}
			,
			{key: 255, question: 'game', answer: 'ゲーム'}
			,
			{key: 256, question: 'game; match; tournament (sports)', answer: 'しあい (試合)'}
			,
			{key: 257, question: 'Germany', answer: 'ドイツ'}
			,
			{key: 258, question: 'to get better; be cured', answer: 'なおる (治る)'}
			,
			{key: 259, question: '"to get empty (おなかがすいている: to be hungry (lit. ""stomach has become empty""))"', answer: 'すく'}
			,
			{key: 260, question: 'to get married', answer: 'けっこんする (結婚する)'}
			,
			{key: 261, question: 'to get off/out of [a vehicle]', answer: 'おりる (降りる)'}
			,
			{key: 262, question: 'to get tired', answer: 'つかれる (疲れる)'}
			,
			{key: 263, question: 'to give', answer: 'あげる'}
			,
			{key: 264, question: 'to give (honorific expression of くれる)', answer: 'くださる ( (long form is くださいます))'}
			,
			{key: 265, question: 'to give (humble expression of あげる)', answer: 'さしあげる'}
			,
			{key: 266, question: "to give (to speaker/person in speaker's in-group)", answer: 'くれる'}
			,
			{key: 267, question: 'to give a presentation', answer: 'はっぴょうする (発表する)'}
			,
			{key: 268, question: 'to give rise to; cause; awaken; raise up', answer: 'おこす (起こす)'}
			,
			{key: 269, question: 'glasses', answer: 'めがね (眼鏡)'}
			,
			{key: 270, question: 'to go', answer: 'いく (行く)'}
			,
			{key: 271, question: 'to go out', answer: 'でかける (出かける)'}
			,
			{key: 272, question: 'to go out; appear; attend', answer: 'でる (出る)'}
			,
			{key: 273, question: 'to go; to come (courteous expression of 行く（いく）and 来る（くる）)', answer: 'まいる (参る)'}
			,
			{key: 274, question: '"to go; to come; to ask (humble expression of 行く（いく）', answer: ' 来る（くる）and 聞く（きく）)" (うかがう)'}
			,
			{key: 275, question: ' (something) goes off/out', answer: 'きえる (消える)'}
			,
			{key: 276, question: 'gold (-colored)', answer: 'きんいろ (金色)'}
			,
			{key: 277, question: 'golf', answer: 'ゴルフ'}
			,
			{key: 278, question: ' (to be) good', answer: 'いい'}
			,
			{key: 279, question: 'Good afternoon.', answer: 'こんにちは'}
			,
			{key: 280, question: 'Good evening.', answer: 'こんばんは'}
			,
			{key: 281, question: 'Good morning.', answer: 'おはようございます'}
			,
			{key: 282, question: ' (to be) good; alright (polite expression of 良い (よい))', answer: 'よろしい'}
			,
			{key: 283, question: 'to graduate', answer: 'そつぎょうする (卒業する)'}
			,
			{key: 284, question: 'grammar', answer: 'ぶんぽう (文法)'}
			,
			{key: 285, question: "[one's own] grandfather (cf. 祖母 (そぼ) [one's own] grandmother)", answer: 'そふ (祖父)'}
			,
			{key: 286, question: 'gray', answer: 'はいいろ (灰色)'}
			,
			{key: 287, question: 'Great Britain; Britain; England; UK', answer: 'イギリス'}
			,
			{key: 288, question: 'green', answer: 'みどり (緑)'}
			,
			{key: 289, question: 'greeting (words said when meeting or parting)', answer: 'あいさつ (挨拶)'}
			,
			{key: 290, question: 'to grow; to raise', answer: 'そだてる (育てる)'}
			,
			{key: 291, question: 'guitar', answer: 'ギター'}
			,
			{key: 292, question: 'hair', answer: 'かみ (髪)'}
			,
			{key: 293, question: 'half past ~; ~ and a half', answer: '～はん (～半)'}
			,
			{key: 294, question: 'hamburger', answer: 'ハンバーガー'}
			,
			{key: 295, question: 'hand', answer: 'て (手)'}
			,
			{key: 296, question: 'hard; rough', answer: 'たいへん（な） (大変（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 297, question: 'hat', answer: 'ぼうし (帽子)'}
			,
			{key: 298, question: 'hated; to hate', answer: 'だいきらい（な） (大嫌い（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 299, question: 'he; boyfriend', answer: 'かれ (彼)'}
			,
			{key: 300, question: 'head', answer: 'あたま (頭)'}
			,
			{key: 301, question: 'to head toward; to face', answer: 'むかう (向かう)'}
			,
			{key: 302, question: 'to hear; listen to; to ask', answer: 'きく (聞く)'}
			,
			{key: 303, question: ' (to be) heavy', answer: 'おもい (重い)'}
			,
			{key: 304, question: 'to help (with)', answer: 'てつだう (手伝う)'}
			,
			{key: 305, question: 'here', answer: 'ここ'}
			,
			{key: 306, question: 'high school', answer: 'こうこう (高校)'}
			,
			{key: 307, question: 'high school student', answer: 'こうこうせい (高校生)'}
			,
			{key: 308, question: ' (to be) high; expensive', answer: 'たかい (高い)'}
			,
			{key: 309, question: 'hiragana', answer: 'ひらがな (平仮名)'}
			,
			{key: 310, question: 'history', answer: 'れきし (歴史)'}
			,
			{key: 311, question: 'hobby', answer: 'しゅみ (趣味)'}
			,
			{key: 312, question: 'to hold; have', answer: 'もつ (持つ)'}
			,
			{key: 313, question: 'homework', answer: 'しゅくだい (宿題)'}
			,
			{key: 314, question: 'Honda [a Japanese company]', answer: 'ホンダ'}
			,
			{key: 315, question: 'hospital', answer: 'びょういん (病院)'}
			,
			{key: 316, question: ' (to be) hot', answer: 'あつい (暑い)'}
			,
			{key: 317, question: '" (to be) hot (written with this kanji', answer: ' refers to the temperature of objects and not to atmospheric temperature)" (あつい)'}
			,
			{key: 318, question: 'hotel', answer: 'ホテル'}
			,
			{key: 319, question: ' (for) ～ hours', answer: '～じかん (～時間)'}
			,
			{key: 320, question: 'house  (honorific expression of 家（うち／いえ）)', answer: 'おたく (お宅)'}
			,
			{key: 321, question: 'house; home', answer: 'うち／いえ (家)'}
			,
			{key: 322, question: 'how', answer: 'どう'}
			,
			{key: 323, question: 'how (politer expression of どう)', answer: 'いかが'}
			,
			{key: 324, question: 'how much', answer: 'いくら'}
			,
			{key: 325, question: 'hundred', answer: 'ひゃく (百)'}
			,
			{key: 326, question: " (one's own) husband", answer: 'しゅじん (主人)'}
			,
			{key: 327, question: 'I (casual, masculine-coded pronoun)', answer: 'おれ (俺)'}
			,
			{key: 328, question: 'I (casual, masculine-coded pronoun)', answer: 'ぼく (僕)'}
			,
			{key: 329, question: 'I; me', answer: 'わたし (私)'}
			,
			{key: 330, question: "I'm sorry (lit. There is no excuse.)", answer: 'もうしわけありません (申し訳ありません)'}
			,
			{key: 331, question: "I'm sorry (lit. There is no excuse.)", answer: 'もうしわけございません (申し訳ございません)'}
			,
			{key: 332, question: "I'm sorry [for what happened]", answer: 'すみませんでした'}
			,
			{key: 333, question: "I'm sorry; excuse me; thank you", answer: 'すみません'}
			,
			{key: 334, question: 'ice cream', answer: 'アイスクリーム'}
			,
			{key: 335, question: 'important', answer: 'たいせつ（な） (大切（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 336, question: 'important; crucial', answer: 'だいじ（な） (大事（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 337, question: 'impossible; more than one can handle', answer: 'むり（な） (無理（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 338, question: 'inconvenient', answer: 'ふべん（な） (不便（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 339, question: 'India', answer: 'インド'}
			,
			{key: 340, question: 'Indonesia', answer: 'インドネシア'}
			,
			{key: 341, question: ' (to be) inexpensive; cheap', answer: 'やすい (安い)'}
			,
			{key: 342, question: 'inside', answer: 'なか (中)'}
			,
			{key: 343, question: 'interest', answer: 'きょうみ (興味)'}
			,
			{key: 344, question: ' (to be) interesting; funny', answer: 'おもしろい (面白い)'}
			,
			{key: 345, question: 'international exchange student; student studying abroad', answer: 'りゅうがくせい (留学生)'}
			,
			{key: 347, question: 'Japan', answer: 'にほん (日本)'}
			,
			{key: 349, question: 'kanji', answer: 'かんじ (漢字)'}
			,
			{key: 350, question: 'karaoke', answer: 'カラオケ'}
			,
			{key: 351, question: 'to keep [as a pet]', answer: 'かう (飼う)'}
			,
			{key: 352, question: '~ kilometers; ~ kilograms', answer: '〜キロ'}
			,
			{key: 353, question: 'kimono; Japanese attire', answer: 'きもの (着物)'}
			,
			{key: 354, question: 'kind', answer: 'しんせつ（な） (親切（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 355, question: ' (to be) kind/gentle; easy/simple', answer: 'やさしい'}
			,
			{key: 356, question: 'to know; learn of', answer: 'しる (知る)'}
			,
			{key: 357, question: 'Kyoto [name of a city]', answer: 'きょうと (京都)'}
			,
			{key: 359, question: 'language of ~', answer: '～ご (～語)'}
			,
			{key: 360, question: 'language; word', answer: 'ことば (言葉)'}
			,
			{key: 361, question: 'last month', answer: 'せんげつ (先月)'}
			,
			{key: 362, question: 'last week', answer: 'せんしゅう (先週)'}
			,
			{key: 363, question: 'last weekend', answer: 'せんしゅうまつ (先週末)'}
			,
			{key: 364, question: 'last year', answer: 'きょねん (去年)'}
			,
			{key: 365, question: ' (to be) late; slow', answer: 'おそい (遅い)'}
			,
			{key: 366, question: 'to laugh; smile', answer: 'わらう (笑う)'}
			,
			{key: 367, question: 'laundry', answer: 'せんたく (洗濯)'}
			,
			{key: 368, question: 'law', answer: 'ほうりつ (法律)'}
			,
			{key: 369, question: 'to learn', answer: 'ならう (習う)'}
			,
			{key: 370, question: 'left', answer: 'ひだり (左)'}
			,
			{key: 371, question: 'to lend', answer: 'かす (貸す)'}
			,
			{key: 372, question: 'letter', answer: 'てがみ (手紙)'}
			,
			{key: 373, question: 'library', answer: 'としょかん (図書館)'}
			,
			{key: 374, question: "life (style); one's living", answer: 'せいかつ (生活)'}
			,
			{key: 375, question: ' (to be) light [in weight]', answer: 'かるい (軽い)'}
			,
			{key: 376, question: 'liked; favorite; to like', answer: 'すき（な） (好き（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 377, question: 'lion', answer: 'ライオン'}
			,
			{key: 378, question: 'to live', answer: 'すむ (住む)'}
			,
			{key: 379, question: 'lively; vigorous; healthy', answer: 'げんき（な） (元気（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 380, question: ' (to be) long', answer: 'ながい (長い)'}
			,
			{key: 381, question: 'to look for; search', answer: 'さがす (探す)'}
			,
			{key: 382, question: 'to look into; look up; examine; investigate', answer: 'しらべる (調べる)'}
			,
			{key: 383, question: 'to lose', answer: 'まける (負ける)'}
			,
			{key: 384, question: 'to lose weight; to get thinner', answer: 'やせる'}
			,
			{key: 385, question: 'loved; to love', answer: 'だいすき（な） (大好き（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 386, question: 'lunch', answer: 'ひるごはん (昼ご飯)'}
			,
			{key: 387, question: 'lunch box', answer: 'おべんとう (お弁当)'}
			,
			{key: 389, question: 'magazine', answer: 'ざっし (雑誌)'}
			,
			{key: 390, question: 'major (at university)', answer: 'せんこう (専攻)'}
			,
			{key: 391, question: 'to make', answer: 'つくる (作る)'}
			,
			{key: 392, question: 'to make a mistake; to be wrong about', answer: 'まちがえる (間違える)'}
			,
			{key: 393, question: 'to make a request; to ask a favor', answer: 'おねがいする (お願いする)'}
			,
			{key: 394, question: 'man', answer: 'おとこ (男)'}
			,
			{key: 395, question: 'mandarin orange', answer: 'みかん'}
			,
			{key: 396, question: 'manga; comic book', answer: 'まんが (漫画)'}
			,
			{key: 397, question: 'many', answer: 'たくさん'}
			,
			{key: 398, question: 'marriage', answer: 'けっこん (結婚)'}
			,
			{key: 399, question: 'maybe', answer: 'たぶん (多分)'}
			,
			{key: 400, question: 'meal', answer: 'ごはん (ご飯)'}
			,
			{key: 401, question: 'meaning', answer: 'いみ (意味)'}
			,
			{key: 402, question: 'meat', answer: 'にく (肉)'}
			,
			{key: 403, question: 'medicine (薬を飲む (くすりをのむ): to take medicine)', answer: 'くすり (薬)'}
			,
			{key: 404, question: 'to meet; to encounter', answer: 'あう (会う)'}
			,
			{key: 405, question: 'meeting; conference', answer: 'かいぎ (会議)'}
			,
			{key: 406, question: "to memorize; commit to memory; fix in one's mind", answer: 'おぼえる (覚える)'}
			,
			{key: 407, question: 'middle school', answer: 'ちゅうがっこう (中学校)'}
			,
			{key: 408, question: 'milk', answer: 'ぎゅうにゅう (牛乳)'}
			,
			{key: 409, question: '~ minutes', answer: '～ふん／ぷん (～分)'}
			,
			{key: 410, question: "~ minutes past ~ o'clock", answer: '～じ～ふん／ぷん (～時～分)'}
			,
			{key: 411, question: 'Monday', answer: 'げつようび (月曜日)'}
			,
			{key: 412, question: 'money', answer: 'おかね (お金)'}
			,
			{key: 413, question: '~ months', answer: '〜かげつ (～か月)'}
			,
			{key: 414, question: 'more', answer: 'もっと'}
			,
			{key: 415, question: 'morning', answer: 'あさ (朝)'}
			,
			{key: 416, question: 'morning; before noon', answer: 'ごぜん (午前)'}
			,
			{key: 417, question: 'mother', answer: 'おかあさん (お母さん)'}
			,
			{key: 418, question: "[one's own] mother", answer: 'はは (母)'}
			,
			{key: 419, question: 'mountain', answer: 'やま (山)'}
			,
			{key: 420, question: 'mouth', answer: 'くち (口)'}
			,
			{key: 421, question: 'to move [houses]', answer: 'ひっこす (引っ越す)'}
			,
			{key: 422, question: 'movie theater', answer: 'えいがかん (映画館)'}
			,
			{key: 423, question: 'movie; film', answer: 'えいが (映画)'}
			,
			{key: 424, question: 'mozzarella cheese', answer: 'モッツァレラチーズ'}
			,
			{key: 425, question: ' (form of address used to refer to children regardless of gender and among women of equal social status)', answer: '〜ちゃん'}
			,
			{key: 426, question: ' (form of address used to refer to men and boys of equal or lower social status)', answer: '〜くん (～君)'}
			,
			{key: 427, question: 'Mr./Ms. ～', answer: '～さん'}
			,
			{key: 428, question: 'Mt. Fuji', answer: 'ふじさん (富士山)'}
			,
			{key: 429, question: 'music', answer: 'おんがく (音楽)'}
			,
			{key: 430, question: 'musical instrument', answer: 'がっき (楽器)'}
			,
			{key: 432, question: 'name', answer: 'なまえ (名前)'}
			,
			{key: 433, question: 'nearby', answer: 'ちかく (近く)'}
			,
			{key: 434, question: 'necklace', answer: 'ネックレス'}
			,
			{key: 435, question: ' (to be) new', answer: 'あたらしい (新しい)'}
			,
			{key: 436, question: 'newspaper', answer: 'しんぶん (新聞)'}
			,
			{key: 437, question: 'next', answer: 'つぎ (次)'}
			,
			{key: 438, question: 'next month', answer: 'らいげつ (来月)'}
			,
			{key: 439, question: 'next to', answer: 'よこ (横)'}
			,
			{key: 440, question: 'next to (something in the same category)', answer: 'となり (隣)'}
			,
			{key: 441, question: 'next week', answer: 'らいしゅう (来週)'}
			,
			{key: 442, question: 'next year', answer: 'らいねん (来年)'}
			,
			{key: 443, question: 'night', answer: 'よる (夜)'}
			,
			{key: 444, question: 'nine', answer: 'きゅう／く (九)'}
			,
			{key: 445, question: 'no', answer: 'いいえ'}
			,
			{key: 446, question: ' (to be) no good', answer: 'いけない'}
			,
			{key: 447, question: 'No problem. (often used instead of いいえ as a response to ありがとうございます in the polite conversation.)', answer: 'いえいえ'}
			,
			{key: 448, question: 'No.1; the first; the most; ~est', answer: 'いちばん (一番)'}
			,
			{key: 449, question: 'nobody; not anyone', answer: 'だれも (誰も [+neg])'}
			,
			{key: 450, question: ' (to be) noisy; loud', answer: 'うるさい (うるさい)'}
			,
			{key: 451, question: 'not at all', answer: 'ぜんぜん  [+neg] (全然)'}
			,
			{key: 452, question: 'not very', answer: 'あまり  [+neg]'}
			,
			{key: 453, question: 'nothing', answer: 'なにも [+neg] (何も)'}
			,
			{key: 454, question: 'now', answer: 'いま (今)'}
			,
			{key: 455, question: 'nowhere; not anywhere', answer: 'どこも (どこも [+neg])'}
			,
			{key: 457, question: "~ o'clock", answer: '～じ (〜時)'}
			,
			{key: 458, question: 'Oceania', answer: 'オセアニア'}
			,
			{key: 459, question: 'office', answer: 'オフィス'}
			,
			{key: 460, question: 'office worker; company employee', answer: 'かいしゃいん (会社員)'}
			,
			{key: 461, question: 'often', answer: 'よく'}
			,
			{key: 462, question: 'oh', answer: 'ああ'}
			,
			{key: 463, question: 'oh! [exclamation of surprise]', answer: 'あっ'}
			,
			{key: 464, question: 'okay', answer: 'だいじょうぶ（な） (大丈夫（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 465, question: ' (to be) old', answer: 'ふるい (古い)'}
			,
			{key: 466, question: "[one's own] older brother", answer: 'あに (兄)'}
			,
			{key: 467, question: 'older brother', answer: 'おにいさん (お兄さん)'}
			,
			{key: 468, question: 'older brother', answer: 'おにいさん (お兄さん)'}
			,
			{key: 469, question: "[one's own] older sister", answer: 'あね (姉)'}
			,
			{key: 470, question: 'older sister', answer: 'おねえさん (お姉さん)'}
			,
			{key: 471, question: 'once again', answer: 'もういちど (もう一度)'}
			,
			{key: 472, question: 'once; first floor', answer: 'いっかい (一回)'}
			,
			{key: 473, question: 'once; one time', answer: 'いちど (一度)'}
			,
			{key: 474, question: 'one', answer: 'いち (一)'}
			,
			{key: 475, question: 'oneself', answer: 'じぶん (自分)'}
			,
			{key: 476, question: 'only ~', answer: '〜だけ'}
			,
			{key: 477, question: 'to open (something)', answer: 'あける (開ける)'}
			,
			{key: 478, question: ' (something) opens', answer: 'あく (開く)'}
			,
			{key: 479, question: 'opinion', answer: 'いけん (意見)'}
			,
			{key: 480, question: 'orange', answer: 'オレンジ'}
			,
			{key: 481, question: 'other than ～', answer: '～いがい (～以外)'}
			,
			{key: 482, question: 'outside', answer: 'そと (外)'}
			,
			{key: 483, question: 'over there', answer: 'あそこ'}
			,
			{key: 484, question: 'over there (casual)', answer: 'あっち'}
			,
			{key: 486, question: 'page', answer: 'ページ'}
			,
			{key: 487, question: ' (to be) painful; to hurt', answer: 'いたい (痛い)'}
			,
			{key: 488, question: 'painting; drawing; picture', answer: 'え (絵)'}
			,
			{key: 489, question: 'parents', answer: 'りょうしん (両親)'}
			,
			{key: 490, question: ' (public) park', answer: 'こうえん (公園)'}
			,
			{key: 491, question: 'part-time work', answer: 'アルバイト'}
			,
			{key: 492, question: 'party', answer: 'パーティー'}
			,
			{key: 493, question: 'passport', answer: 'パスポート'}
			,
			{key: 494, question: 'to pay attention to; to warn', answer: 'ちゅういする (注意する)'}
			,
			{key: 495, question: 'pen', answer: 'ペン'}
			,
			{key: 496, question: 'people', answer: 'ひとびと (人々)'}
			,
			{key: 497, question: 'people of/from ~', answer: '～じん (〜人)'}
			,
			{key: 498, question: 'person', answer: 'ひと (人)'}
			,
			{key: 499, question: 'person (honorific expression of 人（ひと）)', answer: 'かた (方)'}
			,
			{key: 500, question: 'pet', answer: 'ペット'}
			,
			{key: 501, question: 'Philippines', answer: 'フィリピン'}
			,
			{key: 502, question: 'photo; picture', answer: 'しゃしん (写真)'}
			,
			{key: 503, question: 'piano', answer: 'ピアノ'}
			,
			{key: 504, question: 'pink', answer: 'ピンク'}
			,
			{key: 505, question: 'pitiful; pathetic; pitiable', answer: 'かわいそう (かわいそう)'}
			,
			{key: 506, question: 'pizza', answer: 'ピザ'}
			,
			{key: 507, question: 'place', answer: 'ばしょ (場所)'}
			,
			{key: 508, question: 'to place; put', answer: 'おく (置く)'}
			,
			{key: 509, question: 'to play [a stringed instrument]', answer: 'ひく (弾く)'}
			,
			{key: 510, question: 'to play; have fun', answer: 'あそぶ (遊ぶ)'}
			,
			{key: 511, question: 'please give me ~', answer: 'ください (下さい)'}
			,
			{key: 512, question: ' (to be) pleased; glad', answer: 'うれしい (嬉しい)'}
			,
			{key: 513, question: 'pocket', answer: 'ポケット'}
			,
			{key: 514, question: 'to polish; brush [teeth]', answer: 'みがく (磨く)'}
			,
			{key: 515, question: 'polite; careful', answer: 'ていねい（な） (丁寧（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 516, question: 'politely', answer: 'ていねいに (丁寧に)'}
			,
			{key: 517, question: 'popularity', answer: 'にんき (人気)'}
			,
			{key: 518, question: 'pork', answer: 'ぶたにく (豚肉)'}
			,
			{key: 519, question: 'portable; cell phone (abbreviated form of 携帯電話 (けいたいでんわ). also written in katakana: ケータイ.)', answer: 'けいたい (携帯)'}
			,
			{key: 520, question: 'post office', answer: 'ゆうびんきょく (郵便局)'}
			,
			{key: 521, question: 'to practice', answer: 'れんしゅうする (練習する)'}
			,
			{key: 522, question: 'present; gift', answer: 'プレゼント'}
			,
			{key: 523, question: 'presentation; speech', answer: 'はっぴょう (発表)'}
			,
			{key: 524, question: 'pro', answer: 'プロ'}
			,
			{key: 525, question: 'problem', answer: 'もんだい (問題)'}
			,
			{key: 526, question: ' (radio/television etc.) program', answer: 'ばんぐみ (番組)'}
			,
			{key: 527, question: 'project', answer: 'プロジェクト'}
			,
			{key: 528, question: 'to pronounce', answer: 'はつおんする (発音する)'}
			,
			{key: 529, question: 'pronunciation', answer: 'はつおん (発音)'}
			,
			{key: 530, question: 'purple', answer: 'むらさき (紫)'}
			,
			{key: 531, question: 'to push', answer: 'おす (押す)'}
			,
			{key: 532, question: 'to put away; to put back', answer: 'しまう'}
			,
			{key: 533, question: 'to put into', answer: 'いれる (入れる)'}
			,
			{key: 534, question: 'to put on weight; get fat', answer: 'ふとる (太る)'}
			,
			{key: 535, question: 'to put on/wear on the face', answer: 'かける'}
			,
			{key: 536, question: 'to put on/wear on the whole body or upper body', answer: 'きる (着る)'}
			,
			{key: 538, question: "question", answer: 'しつもん (質問)'}
			,
			{key: 539, question: 'quickly; early', answer: 'はやく (早く)'}
			,
			{key: 540, question: 'quiet', answer: 'しずか（な） (静か（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 541, question: 'quietly', answer: 'しずかに (静かに)'}
			,
			{key: 543, question: 'radio', answer: 'ラジオ'}
			,
			{key: 544, question: 'rain', answer: 'あめ (雨)'}
			,
			{key: 545, question: '" (rain', answer: ' snow ( etc.) falls")'}
			,
			{key: 546, question: 'ramen', answer: 'ラーメン'}
			,
			{key: 547, question: 'to read', answer: 'よむ (読む)'}
			,
			{key: 548, question: 'reading; something to read', answer: 'よみもの (読み物)'}
			,
			{key: 549, question: 'really (casual)', answer: 'すごく'}
			,
			{key: 550, question: 'really; truly', answer: 'ほんとうに (本当に)'}
			,
			{key: 551, question: 'to receive', answer: 'もらう'}
			,
			{key: 552, question: 'recently', answer: 'さいきん (最近)'}
			,
			{key: 553, question: ' (the color) red', answer: 'あか (赤)'}
			,
			{key: 554, question: ' (to be) red', answer: 'あかい (赤い)'}
			,
			{key: 555, question: 'refrigerator', answer: 'れいぞうこ (冷蔵庫)'}
			,
			{key: 556, question: 'reply', answer: 'へんじ (返事)'}
			,
			{key: 557, question: 'report', answer: 'レポート'}
			,
			{key: 558, question: 'research', answer: 'けんきゅう (研究)'}
			,
			{key: 559, question: 'research paper', answer: 'ろんぶん (論文)'}
			,
			{key: 560, question: 'respectful language', answer: 'けいご (敬語)'}
			,
			{key: 561, question: 'rest; absence [from class etc.]', answer: 'やすみ (休み)'}
			,
			{key: 562, question: 'to rest; absent [from class etc.]', answer: 'やすむ (休む)'}
			,
			{key: 563, question: 'restaurant', answer: 'レストラン'}
			,
			{key: 564, question: 'to return', answer: 'かえる (帰る)'}
			,
			{key: 565, question: 'to return [something]', answer: 'かえす (返す)'}
			,
			{key: 566, question: 'to review', answer: 'ふくしゅうする (復習する)'}
			,
			{key: 567, question: 'rich person', answer: 'おかねもち (お金持ち)'}
			,
			{key: 568, question: 'to ride; get into/onto [a vehicle]; take [a mode of transportation] (e.g. バスに乗る (のる): to ride a bus)', answer: 'のる (乗る)'}
			,
			{key: 569, question: 'right', answer: 'みぎ (右)'}
			,
			{key: 570, question: 'right away; immediately', answer: 'すぐ'}
			,
			{key: 571, question: 'ring', answer: 'ゆびわ (指輪)'}
			,
			{key: 572, question: 'river', answer: 'かわ (川)'}
			,
			{key: 573, question: 'road', answer: 'みち (道)'}
			,
			{key: 574, question: 'room', answer: 'へや (部屋)'}
			,
			{key: 575, question: 'roommate', answer: 'ルームメート'}
			,
			{key: 576, question: 'rule; regulation', answer: 'きそく (規則)'}
			,
			{key: 577, question: 'to run', answer: 'はしる (走る)'}
			,
			{key: 578, question: 'Russia', answer: 'ロシア'}
			,
			{key: 580, question: ' (to be) sad', answer: 'かなしい (悲しい)'}
			,
			{key: 581, question: 'safe', answer: 'あんぜん（な） (安全（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 582, question: 'sandwich', answer: 'サンドイッチ／サンドウィッチ'}
			,
			{key: 583, question: 'Saturday', answer: 'どようび (土曜日)'}
			,
			{key: 584, question: 'Saudi Arabia', answer: 'サウジアラビア'}
			,
			{key: 585, question: 'to say', answer: 'いう (言う)'}
			,
			{key: 586, question: 'to say (courteous expression of 言う（いう）)', answer: 'もうす (申す)'}
			,
			{key: 587, question: 'to say (honorific expression of 言う（いう）)', answer: 'おっしゃる ( (long form is おっしゃいます))'}
			,
			{key: 588, question: 'to say (humble expression of 言う（いう）)', answer: 'もうしあげる (申し上げる)'}
			,
			{key: 589, question: ' (to be) scary; scared', answer: 'こわい (怖い)'}
			,
			{key: 590, question: 'scholarship; student grant', answer: 'しょうがくきん (奨学金)'}
			,
			{key: 591, question: 'school', answer: 'がっこう (学校)'}
			,
			{key: 592, question: 'science', answer: 'かがく (科学)'}
			,
			{key: 593, question: 'sea; ocean', answer: 'うみ (海)'}
			,
			{key: 594, question: 'season', answer: 'きせつ (季節)'}
			,
			{key: 595, question: 'See you again. (to a friend)', answer: 'じゃあ、また'}
			,
			{key: 596, question: 'to see; watch; look at', answer: 'みる (見る)'}
			,
			{key: 597, question: 'to see; watch; look at ( (humble expression of 拝見する（はいけんする）)', answer: 'はいけんする (拝見する)'}
			,
			{key: 598, question: 'to see; watch; look at (honorific expression of 見る（みる）)', answer: 'ごらんになる (ご覧になる)'}
			,
			{key: 599, question: 'to sell', answer: 'うる (売る)'}
			,
			{key: 600, question: 'sentence', answer: 'ぶん (文)'}
			,
			{key: 601, question: 'Seoul (capital of South Korea)', answer: 'ソウル'}
			,
			{key: 602, question: 'serious; earnest', answer: 'まじめ（な）'}
			,
			{key: 603, question: 'seriously; earnestly', answer: 'まじめに'}
			,
			{key: 604, question: 'seven', answer: 'なな／しち (七)'}
			,
			{key: 605, question: 'she; girlfriend', answer: 'かのじょ (彼女)'}
			,
			{key: 606, question: 'shirt', answer: 'シャツ'}
			,
			{key: 607, question: 'shoe', answer: 'くつ (靴)'}
			,
			{key: 608, question: 'shopping', answer: 'かいもの (買い物)'}
			,
			{key: 609, question: ' (to be) short', answer: 'みじかい (短い)'}
			,
			{key: 610, question: 'short form non-past negative conjugation of ある', answer: 'ない'}
			,
			{key: 611, question: 'to show', answer: 'みせる (見せる)'}
			,
			{key: 612, question: 'shower', answer: 'シャワー'}
			,
			{key: 613, question: 'shower', answer: 'シャワー'}
			,
			{key: 614, question: 'sickness; illness', answer: 'びょうき (病気)'}
			,
			{key: 615, question: 'silver (-colored)', answer: 'ぎんいろ (銀色)'}
			,
			{key: 616, question: 'simple; easy', answer: 'かんたん（な） (簡単（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 617, question: 'to sing', answer: 'うたう (歌う)'}
			,
			{key: 618, question: 'singer', answer: 'かしゅ (歌手)'}
			,
			{key: 619, question: 'to sit; sit down; kneel on the floor', answer: 'すわる (座る)'}
			,
			{key: 620, question: 'site', answer: 'サイト'}
			,
			{key: 621, question: 'six', answer: 'ろく (六)'}
			,
			{key: 622, question: 'skillful; good at', answer: 'じょうず（な） (上手（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 623, question: "skillful; good at (refers to one's confidence rather than objective judgment; used in place of 上手 (じょうず) when the speaker mentions his/her own skills to avoid sounding arrogant)", answer: 'とくい（な） (得意（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 624, question: 'skirt', answer: 'スカート'}
			,
			{key: 625, question: 'to sleep', answer: 'ねる (寝る)'}
			,
			{key: 626, question: 'to sleep (honorific expression of 寝る（ねる）)', answer: 'おやすみになる (お休みになる)'}
			,
			{key: 627, question: ' (to be) small', answer: 'ちいさい (小さい)'}
			,
			{key: 628, question: 'small', answer: 'ちいさく (小さく)'}
			,
			{key: 629, question: 'smartphone', answer: 'スマホ'}
			,
			{key: 630, question: 'to smoke [cigarettes]; to inhale', answer: 'すう (吸う)'}
			,
			{key: 631, question: 'snow', answer: 'ゆき (雪)'}
			,
			{key: 632, question: " (and) so; that's the reason ~", answer: 'だから'}
			,
			{key: 633, question: 'society', answer: 'しゃかい (社会)'}
			,
			{key: 634, question: 'someone', answer: 'だれか (誰か)'}
			,
			{key: 635, question: 'something; anything (in a question)', answer: 'なにか (何か)'}
			,
			{key: 636, question: 'sometime; someday', answer: 'いつか (いつか)'}
			,
			{key: 637, question: 'sometimes', answer: 'ときどき (時々)'}
			,
			{key: 638, question: 'somewhere; anywhere (in a question)', answer: 'どこか (どこか)'}
			,
			{key: 639, question: 'song', answer: 'うた (歌)'}
			,
			{key: 640, question: 'sorry (casual)', answer: 'ごめん'}
			,
			{key: 641, question: 'sound; noise', answer: 'おと (音)'}
			,
			{key: 642, question: 'South Korea', answer: 'かんこく (韓国)'}
			,
			{key: 643, question: 'souvenir; present purchased on a trip', answer: 'おみやげ'}
			,
			{key: 644, question: 'spaghetti', answer: 'スパゲッティー／スパゲティー'}
			,
			{key: 645, question: 'Spain', answer: 'スペイン'}
			,
			{key: 646, question: 'spicy', answer: 'からい (辛い)'}
			,
			{key: 647, question: 'spoon', answer: 'スプーン'}
			,
			{key: 648, question: 'sports', answer: 'スポーツ'}
			,
			{key: 649, question: 'spring', answer: 'はる (春)'}
			,
			{key: 650, question: '"～st/nd/rd/th-year student [e.g. ""first-year student""]"', answer: '～ねんせい (～年生)'}
			,
			{key: 651, question: 'stairs', answer: 'かいだん (階段)'}
			,
			{key: 652, question: 'to stand (up)', answer: 'たつ (立つ)'}
			,
			{key: 653, question: 'station', answer: 'えき (駅)'}
			,
			{key: 654, question: 'to stay at', answer: 'とまる (泊まる)'}
			,
			{key: 655, question: 'to steal', answer: 'ぬすむ (盗む)'}
			,
			{key: 656, question: 'to step on', answer: 'ふむ (踏む)'}
			,
			{key: 657, question: 'still; not yet', answer: 'まだ'}
			,
			{key: 658, question: 'stomach', answer: 'おなか'}
			,
			{key: 659, question: 'store worker', answer: 'てんいん (店員)'}
			,
			{key: 660, question: 'store; shop', answer: 'みせ (店)'}
			,
			{key: 661, question: 'strawberry', answer: 'いちご'}
			,
			{key: 662, question: ' (to be) strict; severe', answer: 'きびしい (厳しい)'}
			,
			{key: 663, question: 'student', answer: 'がくせい (学生)'}
			,
			{key: 664, question: 'to study', answer: 'べんきょうする (勉強する)'}
			,
			{key: 665, question: 'to study abroad', answer: 'りゅうがくする (留学する)'}
			,
			{key: 666, question: 'study (ing)', answer: 'べんきょう (勉強)'}
			,
			{key: 667, question: 'subway', answer: 'ちかてつ (地下鉄)'}
			,
			{key: 668, question: 'sugar', answer: 'さとう (砂糖)'}
			,
			{key: 669, question: 'summer', answer: 'なつ (夏)'}
			,
			{key: 670, question: 'Sunday', answer: 'にちようび (日曜日)'}
			,
			{key: 671, question: 'supermarket', answer: 'スーパー'}
			,
			{key: 672, question: 'to be surprised', answer: 'びっくりする'}
			,
			{key: 673, question: 'sushi', answer: 'すし (寿司)'}
			,
			{key: 674, question: 'sweater', answer: 'セーター'}
			,
			{key: 675, question: 'sweet', answer: 'あまい (甘い)'}
			,
			{key: 676, question: 'sweets; candy; snacks', answer: 'おかし (お菓子)'}
			,
			{key: 677, question: 'to swim', answer: 'およぐ (泳ぐ)'}
			,
			{key: 679, question: 'table', answer: 'テーブル'}
			,
			{key: 680, question: 'to take', answer: 'とる (取る)'}
			,
			{key: 681, question: 'to take [a picture]', answer: 'とる (撮る)'}
			,
			{key: 682, question: 'to take [a shower]', answer: 'あびる (浴びる)'}
			,
			{key: 683, question: 'to take a walk ', answer: 'さんぽする (散歩する)'}
			,
			{key: 684, question: 'take care; get well soon (expression used to someone who is sick)', answer: 'おだいじに (お大事に)'}
			,
			{key: 685, question: '"to take off [clothes', answer: ' shoes ( etc.]")'}
			,
			{key: 686, question: ' (something) takes (time); to cost (money)', answer: 'かかる'}
			,
			{key: 687, question: 'to talk', answer: 'はなす (話す)'}
			,
			{key: 688, question: 'talk; speech', answer: 'はなし (話)'}
			,
			{key: 689, question: 'taxi', answer: 'タクシー'}
			,
			{key: 690, question: 'tea', answer: 'おちゃ (お茶)'}
			,
			{key: 691, question: 'to teach', answer: 'おしえる (教える)'}
			,
			{key: 692, question: 'teacher', answer: 'せんせい (先生)'}
			,
			{key: 693, question: 'team', answer: 'チーム'}
			,
			{key: 694, question: 'telephone', answer: 'でんわ (電話)'}
			,
			{key: 695, question: 'temple', answer: 'おてら (お寺)'}
			,
			{key: 696, question: 'ten', answer: 'じゅう (十)'}
			,
			{key: 697, question: 'ten thousand', answer: 'いちまん (一万)'}
			,
			{key: 698, question: 'ten thousand', answer: 'まん (万)'}
			,
			{key: 699, question: 'tennis', answer: 'テニス'}
			,
			{key: 700, question: 'test', answer: 'しけん (試験)'}
			,
			{key: 701, question: 'textbook', answer: 'きょうかしょ (教科書)'}
			,
			{key: 702, question: 'Thank you.', answer: 'ありがとうございます'}
			,
			{key: 703, question: 'Thank you. (less formal than ありがとうございます.)', answer: 'ありがとう'}
			,
			{key: 704, question: 'that [thing/one close to you]', answer: 'それ'}
			,
			{key: 705, question: 'that [thing/one over there]', answer: 'あれ'}
			,
			{key: 706, question: 'that ~ [close to you]', answer: 'その + Noun'}
			,
			{key: 707, question: 'that ~ [over there]', answer: 'あの + Noun'}
			,
			{key: 708, question: 'that kind of ~ (over there); ~ like that (over there)', answer: 'あんな'}
			,
			{key: 709, question: 'that kind of ~; ~ like that', answer: 'そんな'}
			,
			{key: 710, question: '"that way over there; that over there; over there (politer expression of あっち', answer: ' あれ and あそこ)"'}
			,
			{key: 711, question: 'that way; as you say; so', answer: 'そう'}
			,
			{key: 712, question: '"that way; that; there (politer expression of そっち', answer: ' それ and そこ)"'}
			,
			{key: 713, question: 'the ～th day of the month', answer: '～にち (～日)'}
			,
			{key: 714, question: 'the ～th month of the year', answer: '～げつ (～月)'}
			,
			{key: 715, question: 'the internet', answer: 'インターネット'}
			,
			{key: 716, question: 'the New Year (holidays)', answer: 'おしょうがつ (お正月)'}
			,
			{key: 717, question: 'the sun; day', answer: 'ひ (日)'}
			,
			{key: 718, question: 'the year ～; ～ years', answer: '～ねん (～年)'}
			,
			{key: 719, question: 'there', answer: 'そこ'}
			,
			{key: 720, question: 'thief', answer: 'どろぼう (泥棒)'}
			,
			{key: 721, question: 'thing', answer: 'もの (もの／物)'}
			,
			{key: 722, question: 'thing; (nominalizer that turns the preceding verb into a noun)', answer: 'こと'}
			,
			{key: 723, question: 'to think', answer: 'おもう (思う)'}
			,
			{key: 724, question: 'to think; consider', answer: 'かんがえる (考える)'}
			,
			{key: 725, question: 'this [thing/one]', answer: 'これ'}
			,
			{key: 726, question: 'this ~', answer: 'この + Noun'}
			,
			{key: 727, question: 'this kind of ~; ~ like this', answer: 'こんな'}
			,
			{key: 728, question: 'this month', answer: 'こんげつ (今月)'}
			,
			{key: 729, question: 'this morning', answer: 'けさ (今朝)'}
			,
			{key: 730, question: '"this way; this; here (politer expression of こっち', answer: ' これ and ここ)"'}
			,
			{key: 731, question: 'this week', answer: 'こんしゅう (今週)'}
			,
			{key: 732, question: 'this weekend', answer: 'こんしゅうまつ (今週末)'}
			,
			{key: 733, question: 'this year', answer: 'ことし (今年)'}
			,
			{key: 734, question: 'thousand', answer: 'せん (千)'}
			,
			{key: 735, question: 'three', answer: 'さん (三)'}
			,
			{key: 736, question: 'to throw', answer: 'なげる (投げる)'}
			,
			{key: 737, question: 'to throw away; dispose of', answer: 'すてる (捨てる)'}
			,
			{key: 738, question: 'Thursday', answer: 'もくようび (木曜日)'}
			,
			{key: 739, question: 'ticket', answer: 'きっぷ (切符)'}
			,
			{key: 740, question: 'time', answer: 'じかん (時間)'}
			,
			{key: 741, question: '~ times', answer: '〜かい (～回)'}
			,
			{key: 742, question: 'to paint; draw', answer: 'かく (描く)'}
			,
			{key: 743, question: 'today', answer: 'きょう (今日)'}
			,
			{key: 744, question: 'together', answer: 'いっしょに (一緒に)'}
			,
			{key: 745, question: 'Tokyo [name of a city]', answer: 'とうきょう (東京)'}
			,
			{key: 746, question: 'tomorrow', answer: 'あした (明日)'}
			,
			{key: 747, question: 'tonight', answer: 'こんばん (今晩)'}
			,
			{key: 748, question: 'tooth', answer: 'は (歯)'}
			,
			{key: 749, question: 'town', answer: 'まち (町)'}
			,
			{key: 750, question: 'Toyota [a Japanese company]', answer: 'トヨタ'}
			,
			{key: 751, question: 'train', answer: 'でんしゃ (電車)'}
			,
			{key: 752, question: 'to travel', answer: 'りょこうする (旅行する)'}
			,
			{key: 753, question: 'travel; trip', answer: 'りょこう (旅行)'}
			,
			{key: 754, question: 'T-shirt', answer: 'Tシャツ (ティーシャツ)'}
			,
			{key: 755, question: 'tsunami', answer: 'つなみ (津波)'}
			,
			{key: 756, question: 'Tuesday', answer: 'かようび (火曜日)'}
			,
			{key: 757, question: 'to turn off; put out (something)', answer: 'けす (消す)'}
			,
			{key: 758, question: 'to turn on (something); bring together; attach; affix', answer: 'つける'}
			,
			{key: 759, question: ' (something) turns on; attaches', answer: 'つく'}
			,
			{key: 760, question: 'TV', answer: 'テレビ'}
			,
			{key: 761, question: 'two', answer: 'に (二)'}
			,
			{key: 762, question: 'two people', answer: 'ふたり (二人)'}
			,
			{key: 764, question: '"uh-uh [casual form of ""no""]"', answer: 'ううん'}
			,
			{key: 765, question: 'umbrella', answer: 'かさ (傘)'}
			,
			{key: 766, question: ' (to be) uncommon; rare', answer: 'めずらしい (珍しい)'}
			,
			{key: 767, question: 'to understand; to know', answer: 'わかる (分かる)'}
			,
			{key: 768, question: 'university; college', answer: 'だいがく (大学)'}
			,
			{key: 769, question: 'unskillful; bad at', answer: 'へた（な） (下手（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 770, question: "unskillful; bad at (refers to one's lack of confidence rather than objective judgment.)", answer: 'にがて（な） (苦手（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 771, question: 'up; above', answer: 'うえ (上)'}
			,
			{key: 772, question: 'to use', answer: 'つかう (使う)'}
			,
			{key: 773, question: 'usually', answer: 'たいてい'}
			,
			{key: 775, question: 'various', answer: 'いろいろ（な） (色々（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 776, question: 'vegetable', answer: 'やさい (野菜)'}
			,
			{key: 777, question: 'very', answer: 'とても'}
			,
			{key: 778, question: 'very soon', answer: 'もうすぐ'}
			,
			{key: 779, question: 'Vietnam', answer: 'ベトナム'}
			,
			{key: 780, question: 'volunteer work', answer: 'ボランティア'}
			,
			{key: 782, question: 'to wait', answer: 'まつ (待つ)'}
			,
			{key: 783, question: 'to wake up; get up; (something) happens', answer: 'おきる (起きる)'}
			,
			{key: 784, question: 'to walk', answer: 'あるく (歩く)'}
			,
			{key: 785, question: 'wallet', answer: 'さいふ (財布)'}
			,
			{key: 786, question: ' (to be) wanted; to want', answer: 'ほしい (欲しい)'}
			,
			{key: 787, question: 'war', answer: 'せんそう (戦争)'}
			,
			{key: 788, question: 'warm', answer: 'あたたかい (暖かい)'}
			,
			{key: 789, question: 'wasabi', answer: 'わさび'}
			,
			{key: 790, question: 'to wash', answer: 'あらう (洗う)'}
			,
			{key: 791, question: 'water', answer: 'みず (水)'}
			,
			{key: 792, question: 'water bed', answer: 'ウォーターベッド'}
			,
			{key: 793, question: 'way (of doing something)', answer: 'しかた (仕方)'}
			,
			{key: 794, question: 'we; us', answer: 'わたしたち (私達)'}
			,
			{key: 795, question: 'weather', answer: 'てんき (天気)'}
			,
			{key: 796, question: 'weather forecast; weather report', answer: 'てんきよほう (天気予報)'}
			,
			{key: 797, question: 'Wednesday', answer: 'すいようび (水曜日)'}
			,
			{key: 798, question: 'weekend', answer: 'しゅうまつ (週末)'}
			,
			{key: 799, question: '"well then; in that case [used when beginning or ending a topic or when transitioning to a new', answer: ' related topic]"'}
			,
			{key: 800, question: 'what', answer: 'なに／なん (何)'}
			,
			{key: 801, question: 'What happened? (lit. How did you do?)', answer: 'どうしたんですか／どうしたの？'}
			,
			{key: 802, question: 'what kind of ～', answer: 'どんな～'}
			,
			{key: 803, question: 'when', answer: 'いつ'}
			,
			{key: 804, question: 'when ～', answer: '～とき (〜時)'}
			,
			{key: 805, question: 'where', answer: 'どこ'}
			,
			{key: 806, question: 'which [one]', answer: 'どれ'}
			,
			{key: 807, question: 'which ~', answer: 'どの + Noun'}
			,
			{key: 808, question: '"which way; which; where (politer expressions of どっち', answer: ' どれ and どこ)"'}
			,
			{key: 809, question: 'whichever', answer: 'どれでも (どれでも)'}
			,
			{key: 810, question: ' (the color) white', answer: 'しろ (白)'}
			,
			{key: 811, question: ' (to be) white', answer: 'しろい (白い)'}
			,
			{key: 812, question: 'who', answer: 'だれ (誰)'}
			,
			{key: 813, question: 'who  (honorific expression of 誰（だれ）)', answer: 'どなた'}
			,
			{key: 814, question: 'why', answer: 'どうして'}
			,
			{key: 815, question: ' (to be) wide; spacious', answer: 'ひろい (広い)'}
			,
			{key: 816, question: 'window', answer: 'まど (窓)'}
			,
			{key: 817, question: 'winter', answer: 'ふゆ (冬)'}
			,
			{key: 818, question: "with all one's effort (can be used as adverb (e.g. 一生懸命走る (いっしょうけんめいはしる) run with all one's effort)", answer: 'いっしょうけんめい（な） (一生懸命（な）)'}
			,
			{key: 819, question: 'woman', answer: 'おんな (女)'}
			,
			{key: 820, question: 'word', answer: 'ご (語)'}
			,
			{key: 821, question: 'word; vocabulary', answer: 'たんご (単語)'}
			,
			{key: 822, question: 'to work', answer: 'はたらく (働く)'}
			,
			{key: 823, question: 'to work for; to be employed at', answer: 'つとめる (勤める)'}
			,
			{key: 824, question: 'to work hard; to stick with something', answer: 'がんばる (頑張る)'}
			,
			{key: 825, question: 'work; job', answer: 'しごと (仕事)'}
			,
			{key: 826, question: 'world', answer: 'せかい (世界)'}
			,
			{key: 827, question: 'to worry', answer: 'しんぱいする (心配する)'}
			,
			{key: 828, question: 'to write', answer: 'かく (書く)'}
			,
			{key: 830, question: '"yeah [casual form of ""yes""]"', answer: 'うん'}
			,
			{key: 831, question: '～ years old', answer: '～さい (～歳)'}
			,
			{key: 832, question: ' (the color) yellow', answer: 'きいろ (黄色)'}
			,
			{key: 833, question: ' (to be) yellow', answer: 'きいろい (黄色い)'}
			,
			{key: 834, question: 'yes', answer: 'はい'}
			,
			{key: 835, question: 'yesterday', answer: 'きのう (昨日)'}
			,
			{key: 836, question: 'you', answer: 'あなた'}
			,
			{key: 837, question: "[one's own] younger brother", answer: 'おとうと (弟)'}
			,
			{key: 838, question: 'younger brother', answer: 'おとうと（さん） (弟（さん）)'}
			,
			{key: 839, question: "[one's own] younger sister", answer: 'いもうと (妹)'}
			,
			{key: 840, question: 'younger sister', answer: 'いもうと（さん） (妹（さん）)'}
		]
    }
]